<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tajik English</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Alphabet">  Алифбо</string>
    <string name="Number"> Рақамҳо</string>
    <string name="topic">Топик</string>
    <string name="Words">Калимаҳо</string>
    <string name="Units">Бобҳо</string>
    <string name="Phrases">Ибораҳо</string>
    <string name="speechtext">Cуханрони</string>
    <string name="foreigntopic">Хориҷӣ</string>
    <string name="vocabularytopic">луғат</string>
    <string name="questionstopic">Савол</string>
    <string name="irregular_verbs">Феълҳои нодуруст</string>
    <string name="speechtotext">Талаффуз</string>
    <string name="stoptotext">Ором</string>
    <string name="englishtajik">Тоҷики-Англисӣ</string>
    <string name="tajikenglish">Англисӣ-Тоҷики</string>
    <string name="topic1">I want to be an interpreter. It is an interesting and useful profession. My parents have a large library and they taught me to like books. I like reading books. My favourite subjects in school are English, Literature, Geography and History. My favourite English and American writers are Shakespeare, Dickens, Walter Scott, Jack London, Mark Twain.

Once at the class of Literature, our teacher told us that, when translated, literary works lose much of their beauty. She said that poetry is very hard to translate. From that day I have a dream. I want to have my favourite books in the original and to know the languages they are written in. So I will enjoy the real beauty of these books.

I also like reading books about other countries and cultures. It is so interesting to learn that other people think differently.

I want to become an interpreter because of some reasons. It is an interesting profession because an interpreter meets people from different countries and cultures all the time and has an opportunity to learn much about them. Besides, this profession is very useful because it helps people to understand each other.</string>
</resources>